THE CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
本剧的人物、组织和 事件均为虚构
TWO DAYS BEFORE
两天前
Hey,
嘿，
can your boss get him back up?
你的老板能让他回来吗？
Yes, he feels better.
是的，他感觉好多了。
It would be humiliating
这将是一种耻辱
to become impotent over something like that, right?
对这样的事情变得无能为力，对吗？
And.
和。
By the way,
顺便一提，
I saw a girl like that next to Jung Gicheul.
我 在郑基哲身边看到了一个这样的女孩。
Do you know who she is?
你知道她是谁吗？
When your gangs fought,
当你们的帮派打斗时，
there was supposed to be a girl there.
那里应该有一个女孩。
-Correct. -Who the hell is that?
-正确的。 -那到底是谁？
Our men say
我们男人说
she is a police officer.
她是一名警察。
From the SMPA or something.
来自 SMPA 之类的。
The SMPA?
SMPA？
Nonsense, you idiots.
胡说八道，你们这些白痴。
No really.
不完全是。
SMPA. Kiss my ass.
SMPA。吻我的屁股。
Why should I come all this way?
我为什么要 千里迢迢而来？
You could have come to me.
你本来可以来找我的。
Hey.
嘿。
I'll keep it short.
我会长话短说。
Could you check if this person is with the SMPA?
您能查一下 此人是否是 SMPA 的成员吗？
I know you.
我认识你。
She is the daughter of one.
她是其中一人的女儿。
From whom?
从谁？
What was the name of the former commissioner?
前任专员叫什么名字？
Yu Dukhoon?
余德勋？
This is his daughter.
这是他的女儿。
-Real? -Yes.
-真实的？ -是的。
A well-known police family.
著名的警察世家。
Commissioner Yu's two sons,
于专员的两个儿子，
his daughter, even the son-in-law. All police officers.
他的女儿，甚至女婿。 所有警察。
Son in law? Then she is married.
女婿？然后她结婚了。
Or divorced?
还是离婚了？
In a police family? Never.
出身于警察家庭？绝不。
What do you say about that?
对此你有何看法？
A married policewoman and a gangster?
已婚女警察 和歹徒？
How?
如何？
Are you quite sure?
你确定吗？
No confusion? That is her?
没有混乱吗？那是她？
Look.
看。
Do you want to live here?
你想住在这里吗？
This will be our house.
这将是我们的房子。
Once this deal is completed,
一旦这笔交易完成，
I'll start over here.
我将从这里开始。
Will you be there?
你会在那儿吗？
Gicheul.
吉舍尔。
Isn't it nice here?
这里不是很好吗？
Because of this deal...
因为这笔交易...
Does it still have to be there?
它还必须在那里吗？
I have to see it through.
我必须把它看完。
Everything will be fine. No worries.
一切都会好起来的。不用担心。
Junmo, can't you stop here?
君莫，你就不能停在这里吗？
If you prevent trade...
如果你阻止贸易...
If you just stop now,
如果你现在停下来
then nothing will happen to us.
那么我们就不会发生任何事情。
Who is “us”?
谁是？？？我们？？？
Euijeong, is it...
义正，是吗……
... because of Jung Gicheul?
……因为郑基哲？
Junmo.
Junmo.
I can ...
我可以 ...
...don't stop here.
...不要停在这里。
I will close this case.
我会结掉这个案子。
THE WORST OF EVIL
最邪恶的事
The number is correct.
号码是正确的。
Let's finish it.
让我们完成它吧。
Hello. Did you find out anything?
你好。你有发现什么吗？
-Yes. -The name again?
-是的。 -再说一遍名字吗？
Officer Park Junmo.
朴俊模警官。
- Park Junmo. -Ja.
- 朴俊模。 -贾。
-POLICE CHIEF? -Yes.
-警察局长？ -是的。
-Next time it's my turn. -What?
-下次轮到我了。 -什么？
Thanks.
谢谢。
Who is this?
这是谁？
A clueless policeman,
一个无知的警察，
whose wife cheats on him with a gangster.
他的妻子 和一个歹徒一起欺骗了他。
"Park Junmo"?
“朴俊模”？
Jung Gicheul, you son of a bitch.
郑基哲你个王八蛋。
I will have you at any cost
我会不惜一切代价拥有你
put behind bars.
关进监狱。
You have the material.
你有材料。
Good. Stay close on their heels.
好的。紧跟 他们的脚步。
Well done.
做得好。
I quickly go to the toilet.
我赶紧去厕所。
WC
厕所
We're leaving, sir.
我们要走了，先生。
Captain, the black limousine has been there the whole time.
队长，黑色豪华轿车 一直在那儿。
Don't jump to conclusions.
不要急于下结论。
We arrest the suspects when they load the boat.
当嫌疑人 装船时我们将其逮捕。
Yongdae, it's me.
永大，是我。
Hallo, Boss.
你好，老板。
Find out if Chief Seo is in Gangnam.
查一下徐局长是否在江南。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
Why are you taking this all personally?
你为什么把这 一切都当成是针对你个人的？
Because it's dangerous.
因为这很危险。
That's why I have to do this.
这就是为什么我必须这样做。
Plus, I started it.
另外，我开始了。
I saw it as the only way I could live my life
我认为这是我生活的唯一方式
and could change that of my men .
并且可以改变我手下的情况。
But you keep that a secret from them.
但你要对他们保密。
If they knew drug money paid for their stores,
如果他们知道 为他们的商店支付了毒品资金
they would feel guilty.
他们会感到内疚。
Seung Ho.
胜浩
At some point I started
在某个时刻我开始
to recognize myself in you.
在你身上认出我自己。
You pursue your goals
你追求你的目标
stubborn and unyielding.
顽固不屈。
That's why I trust you with this.
这就是为什么我在这件事上信任你。
It will not be easy,
没那么简单，
but I wish you luck.
但我祝你好运。
Ok, Sir.
好的，先生。
But if it gets too dangerous,
但如果事情变得太危险
then you have to stop.
那么你必须停下来。
By the way, where does the trading actually take place?
顺便问一下， 交易实际上是在哪里进行的？
Here.
这里。
Port Seven.
七号港。
Is the dealer Japanese?
经销商是日本人吗？
A Korean-Japanese skipper.
韩日混血船长。
He speaks Korean fluently, you can talk to him directly.
他韩语说得很流利， 你可以直接和他交谈。
He just got out.
他刚出来。
Is the car already at the entrance?
车已经到门口了吗？
I don't see anyone yet.
我还没有看到任何人。
Shin, look at it.
欣，你看一下。
OK, sir. I'll drive over.
好的，先生。我开车过去。
Seung Ho.
胜浩
Wake up.
醒来。
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
Captain, I think we missed her.
队长，我想 我们想念她了。
Crap.
废话。
Captain.
队长。
A car exploded on the street near the harbor.
一辆汽车在港口附近的街道上爆炸。
Exploded?
爆炸了？
Check it out on site.
现场查看一下。
Damned.
该死的。
Come on. Wake up.
快点。醒来。
Boss.
老板。
What just happened?
刚刚发生了什么？
What about our fabric?
我们的布料呢？
He is gone.
他已经去了。
Damned.
该死的。
What's going on here?
这里发生了什么？
What happened?
发生了什么？
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
Get on.
进行。
Kyungjin?
京津？
How did he know you were here?
他怎么知道 你在这里？
That must have been Jungbae.
那一定是正裴吧。
Nobody knows this route,
没有人知道这条路，
except him, you and me.
除了他，还有你和我。
That was 30 kilograms.
那是30公斤。
These bastards.
这些混蛋。
I spare them and they betray me.
我饶恕了他们 ，他们却背叛了我。
-Let's go to the hospital. -No.
-我们去医院吧。 -不。
Let's go to Seoul.
我们去首尔吧。
Seoul? Why?
汉城？为什么？
We have to find the material first.
我们首先要找到材料。
Go ahead, go ahead!
加油，加油！
Back to Seoul.
返回首尔。
And gather the boys.
并聚集男孩们。
-What happened? -I was there.
-发生了什么？ -我在那里。
The exploded car was our target.
爆炸的汽车 是我们的目标。
But there was no one inside.
但里面并没有人。
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
We're retreating to Seoul for now.
我们 现在要撤退到首尔了。
Yes, Captain.
是的，船长。
What did he say?
他说什么？
Back to Seoul.
返回首尔。
Damned!
该死！
What the hell is going on?
这到底是怎么回事？
Boss, are you okay?
老板，你还好吗？
Choi Jungbae and Oh Kyungjin betrayed us.
崔正培和吴庆镇 背叛了我们。
- Byungwoo. -And, Sir?
- 秉宇。 -那么，先生？
What is Kyungjin up to today?
京津今天在忙什么？
I don't know, sir. He disappeared without a trace.
我不知道，先生。 他消失得无影无踪。
Search every corner and find these motherfuckers.
搜遍每一个角落 ，找到这些混蛋。
Why are you standing there so stupid?
你为什么傻站在那里？
Come on! Move your asses!
快点！动动你的屁股！
-Yes, sir! -Let's go.
-是的先生！ -我们走吧。
This is the list of dealers we know.
这是我们所知道的经销商名单 。
We start grilling them immediately.
我们 立即开始烧烤它们。
Find out by any means possible whether they have recently
通过任何可能的方式查明 他们最近是否
had contact with Jungbae.
与郑培有过接触。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
One day you realize
有一天你意识到
that you were blind.
你是盲目的。
All dealers from Gangnam Crystal.
所有经销商均来自江南水晶。
Jung Gicheul has his people search all of Gangnam,
郑基哲让他的人 搜索整个江南，
so I think they will find Choi Jungbae soon.
所以我想 他们很快就会找到崔正裴。
When Choi and Oh were in our gang,
当崔和吴 在我们帮里时
Those were their phone numbers.
这些是他们的电话号码。
Check their call logs.
检查他们的通话记录。
I made a risky decision and trusted you.
我做了一个冒险的决定 并信任你。
You disappoint me, Mr. Jung.
你让我失望了，郑先生。
This will cause great damage,
这会造成很大的伤害，
not only for me, but also for you.
不仅为了我， 也为了你。
I am very sorry.
我很抱歉。
I will send it to you at any cost.
我会不惜一切代价把它寄给你。
I'll give you a week.
我给你一周的时间。
I can't wait any longer.
我不能再等了。
I understand.
我明白。
I will show no more mercy.
我不会 再有任何怜悯。
What did he say?
他说什么？
One week.
一周。
We really need to find this stuff.
我们确实需要找到这个东西。
Naturally.
自然。
That was our lifelong dream. Of course we have to find it.
那是我们一生的梦想。 当然我们必须找到它。
I'll go then.
那我就去吧
However, Gicheul...
然而，吉切尔...
... to be honest,
... 说实话，
I don't see any point in it. We already own all of Gangnam.
我不认为这有什么意义。 我们已经拥有了整个江南区。
I mean,
我是说，
Every day there is new trouble and it becomes more and more dangerous.
每天都有新的麻烦 ，而且变得越来越危险。
The boys express their concerns.
男孩们表达了他们的担忧。
Are you saying we should give up now?
你是说 我们现在应该放弃吗？
And?
和？
I'm just saying, we can sure...
我只是说， 我们可以确定...
Fuck it safe!
去他妈的安全！
Gut.
肠道。
I understand.
我明白。
POLICE OFFICE EUMSEONG DEPARTMENT FIGHTING CRIME
阴城警察局 打击犯罪
Definition of province, what?
省的定义是什么？
Good afternoon, gentlemen police officers!
警察先生们下午好！
Oh, you're all alone.
哦，你一个人。
Man, you need to clean this place up.
伙计，你需要清理这个地方。
How can I help you?
我怎么帮你？
I am an investigator with Gangnam Police in Seoul.
我是 首尔江南警察局的一名调查员。
Understand.
理解。
Is Detective Park Junmo here?
朴俊模侦探在吗？
I would like to visit him.
我想去拜访他。
He is currently ill.
他目前生病了。
Was?
曾是？
Written in sick?
写的是生病吗？
Is he very sick?
他病得很重吗？
No, I don't think it's that serious.
不，我 不认为事情有那么严重。
What could be going on?
可能发生什么事？
His wife certainly cooks well for him and everything.
他的妻子 为他做的饭菜当然很好吃。
I know trusting me was a hard decision.
我知道信任我 是一个艰难的决定。
And then my first trade goes wrong.
然后 我的第一笔交易就出错了。
I apologize.
我道歉。
At least my judgment of character is confirmed.
至少我的性格判断得到了 证实。
You didn't run away
你没有逃跑
you told me everything honestly.
你诚实地告诉了我一切。
Producing the material again is easy,
再次生产材料很容易，
not finding a trustworthy person .
没有找到一个值得信赖的人。
Haeryun, I will do everything I can to find the material
海云，我会尽一切努力 寻找素材
and save this trade.
并保存这笔交易。
Somehow I'm always in your debt.
不知怎的，我 总是欠你的情。
Then pay them.
然后付钱给他们。
I trust you.
我相信你。
I know you'll make everything okay.
我知道你会让 一切顺利。
Seung Ho.
胜浩
How depressed you are.
你有多郁闷啊。
I like you because you are confident.
我喜欢你 ，因为你有自信。
Don't burden yourself with everything alone.
不要独自承担所有事情的负担。
Tell me if you need help.
如果您需要帮助请告诉我。
Your worries are mine too.
你的担忧也是我的。
Your father in China must be very upset too.
你在中国的父亲 一定也很伤心吧。
I'm just ...
我只是 ...
...worried that I'm getting you in trouble.
……担心给 你带来麻烦。
That concerns me.
这让我很担心。
I do this because I want to.
我这样做是因为我想这么做。
So don't feel bad.
所以不要感觉不好。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I like the smell of the water.
我喜欢水的味道。
I smelled that every morning.
我每天早上都闻到这个味道。
Did you live by a river?
你住在河边吗？
Ja, am Yitong.
Ja, am Yitong.
In Changchun. It's beautiful there.
在长春。那里很漂亮。
Changchun?
长春？
And.
和。
It's peaceful there.
那里很安静。
Quieter than here.
比这里安静。
-Hello? -It's me.
-你好？ -这就是我。
Hallo, Boss.
你好，老板。
Something happened?
发生了一些事？
Is Haeryun objective about this boy, Kwon Seungho?
海润 对权胜浩这个男孩客观吗？
This weak girl was bound to cause problems.
这个柔弱的女孩， 注定会惹出麻烦。
She has to take responsibility.
她必须承担责任。
Damned!
该死！
Haeryun.
海云。
Do you want to wait in China?
你想在中国等吗？
The situation in Korea doesn't seem very good.
韩国的情况 似乎不太好。
When looking for the material,
在寻找素材的时候，
who knows what will happen.
谁知道会发生什么。
When it's clarified,
当事情澄清后，
we go together.
我们一起去。
Let's drive.
我们开车吧。
Dohyung.
道亨。
I now know where the Chinese are.
我现在知道 中国人在哪里了。
Changchun, Jilin.
Changchun, Jilin.
From Korea we know of their base in Changchun
从韩国我们知道 他们的基地在长春
and questioned the local police about the Korean-Chinese gangs.
并向当地警方询问了有关 韩裔华人团伙的情况。
The gang is called Donghobang.
该团伙名为“东湖帮”。
Your boss is Lee Oson.
你的老板是李奥森。
Our Korean source has been confirmed
我们的韩国来源 已经确认
his daughter is Lee Haeryun.
他的女儿是李海润。
We leave for Changchun immediately.
我们立即出发前往长春。
We locate their drug factory with the help of the police there
我们在警察的帮助下找到了他们的制药厂
and wait for Korea and Japan to give us the signal to arrest.
等待韩国和日本 向我们发出逮捕信号。
Understood?
明白了吗？
Yes, sir!
是的先生！
Good. Listen again.
好的。再听一遍。
OK. The Chinese are ready.
好的。中国人已经准备好了。
All thanks to Detective Park,
多亏了朴侦探，
who plays with Haeryun's heart.
谁玩弄了海云的心。
Sir.
先生。
Now let's find Choi Jungbae...
现在我们去找崔政培吧...
No, let's make the entire investigation public now .
不行，我们现在就把整个调查过程公开吧。
You're joking, right?
你在开玩笑吧？
Things are getting riskier for Detective Park.
朴侦探的处境变得越来越危险 。
Officer Yu is also worried.
于警官也很担心。
-And? -What do you mean by "and"?
-和？ -“和”是什么意思？
Captain!
队长！
We are nearly there.
我们快到了。
Please keep the focus until it's over.
请保持焦点 直到结束。
-Sir. -I'm serious.
-先生。 -我是认真的。
And calm down Officer Yu.
让于警官冷静一下。
We cannot reveal the couple's private feelings
我们不能透露 夫妻俩的私人感受
allow the investigation to be compromised.
让调查受到损害。
Welcome back, sir.
欢迎回来，先生。
Would you like me to drive you to the office, sir?
先生，需要我开车送您去办公室吗？
I wonder why things keep happening.
我想知道 为什么事情不断发生。
Why does shit like this keep happening to us ?
为什么这样的事总是发生在我们身上 ？
Sir.
先生。
The boss told me to do something first.
老板让我 先做点事。
Was?
曾是？
The document is in the glove compartment.
该文件位于手套箱中。
Yongdae, drive me back to Gangnam Police.
龙大，开车送我回 江南警察局。
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
SEOUL POLICE DEPARTMENT
首尔警察厅
I was always with the SMPA,
我一直和 SMPA 在一起，
just not the security department.
只是不是安全部门。
Something happened, right?
有事发生了，对吧？
Guys who used to work for Jung Gicheul stole the meth.
曾经 为郑基哲工作的人偷走了冰毒。
Then the trade stopped?
然后交易就停止了？
How is Junmo?
君莫怎么样了？
Junmo is safe and well.
君莫安然无恙。
But why did these police officers want to find Junmo in Eumseong?
但这些警察为什么要 到阴城去找俊模呢？
What do you mean by that?
你是什​​么意思？
Detective Hwang Mingoo.
黄民高侦探。
He was at Eumseong Police Station yesterday.
昨天他 在阴城警察局。
Detective Hwang.
黄侦探。
I heard you're looking for me.
我听说你在找我。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Park Junmo of Eumseong Police.
阴城警察局的朴俊模。
Understand. Detective Park Junmo.
理解。侦探朴俊模。
I think I've seen that one before.
我想 我以前见过那个。
Wen?
温？
Maybe not.
也许不会。
Was?
曾是？
Oh Mann.
哦曼。
Why did you want to see me?
你为什么想见我？
I was told you were on leave due to illness,
我听说 你因病请假
but you seem healthy.
但你看起来很健康。
Alongside,
旁边，
Inspector Yu Euijeong is your wife, right?
柳义正警官是你的妻子吧？
Yes. And?
是的。和？
Yu Euijeongs Ehemann, Park Junmo.
余义正、埃赫曼、朴俊模。
Why does he come and meet Hwang Mingoo here?
他为什么会来 这里和黄民浩见面呢？
Park Junmo?
朴俊模？
Is he the husband of our boss's girlfriend?
他是我们老板女朋友的丈夫吗？
Well, I don't even know where to start.
好吧，我什至不知道 从哪里开始。
Did you know,
你可知道，
that your wife is cheating on you?
你的妻子在欺骗你吗？
Of course not.
当然不是。
This handsome boy's name is Jung Gicheul.
这个帅哥的名字叫郑基哲。
A gangster in Gangnam.
江南的一个黑帮。
The lady next to him is your wife, right?
他旁边的那位女士 是你的妻子，对吗？
Yes. And?
是的。和？
What do you mean by saying, "Yes, and?"
你说 “是的，并且”是什么意思？
This is strange.
这很奇怪。
Your wife is having a good time with another man.
你的妻子正在和另一个男人玩得很开心 。
Doesn't that bother you?
这不困扰你吗？
Stay out of our family matters
远离 我们的家庭事务
and take care of your own.
并照顾好自己的。
What? How can you say that?
什么？你怎么能这么说呢？
I'm telling you this for your own good.
我告诉你这些都是为了你好。
My family is my business.
我的家庭就是我的事业。
Was?
曾是？
You still look quite young.
你看起来还是很年轻。
Do you want to retire yet?
你还想退休吗？
How can you talk to me like that?
你怎么可以这样跟我说话？
It makes me sick to see you playing detective.
看到你扮演侦探让我感到恶心。
I will go now.
我要走了。
Exactly!
确切地！
I know it again! I saw him.
我又知道了！ 我看到了他。
Wo?
沃？
When I went to get the document for the boss,
当我去给老板拿文件的时候，
that's when I saw him.
就在那时我看到了他。
I am certain.
我确信。
I'm smart.
我很聪明。
What the hell is going on here?
这到底是怎么回事？
We can't find this meth park on the list .
我们在名单上找不到这个冰毒公园。
If we don't fix this,
如果我们不解决这个问题
we'll have big problems.
我们将会遇到大问题。
I called his pager.
我拨通了他的传呼机。
He will definitely contact us.
他一定会联系我们的。
What? He contacts us?
什么？他联系我们？
You piece of shit.
你这个废物。
Come with me.
跟我来。
Come with me, you son of a bitch.
跟我来吧，你这个王八蛋。
You go now and do what the fuck you have to do,
你现在就去做 你他妈必须做的事吧
and bring me that bastard Meth Park.
把那个混蛋冰毒公园带给我。
-Go get him! -Seungho.
-去找他！ -胜浩。
Can we talk for a moment?
我们可以聊一会儿吗？
In such times
在这样的时代
we have to keep a cool head.
我们必须 保持冷静的头脑。
The lost material was millions...
损失的材料达数百万...
No, worth billions of won.
不，价值数十亿韩元。
That can destroy everything.
那可以摧毁一切。
We know this!
我们知道这一点！
Our boys are working their asses off to find him!
我们的孩子们正在拼命 寻找他！
Who did they find with their worked asses?
他们辛辛苦苦找到了谁？
What did you just say?
你刚刚说什么？
Enough.
足够的。
Say that again.
再说一次。
Moderate yourself. I'm Hong Heesung.
自我节制。 我是洪熙成。
Hong Heesung.
洪熙成.
Check all our graduates,
检查 我们所有的毕业生，
whether anyone is in contact with Jungbae or Kyungjin.
是否有人与 Jungbae 或 Kyungjin 有联系 。
You asshole ...
你这个混蛋...
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Go.
去。
We will talk later.
我们过一会再聊。
Boss, I met Haeryun a few days ago.
老大，我 前几天见到了海云。
Because we lost all the material
因为我们失去了所有的材料
and they didn't pay,
而且他们没有付钱，
They seem to have problems.
他们似乎有问题。
It's all gone.
一切都消失了。
Was?
曾是？
When we got the material,
当我们拿到材料后，
Choi Jungbae came to our office and took everything with him.
崔正培 带着所有东西来到我们的办公室。
Holy shit!
天啊！
Choi Jungbae, that damn bastard.
崔正培这个混蛋。
Boss, does he have family or relatives?
老板，他有家人或亲戚吗？
Shouldn't we take them on?
我们不应该接受他们吗？
and find out where he is?
并找出他在哪里？
Seung Ho.
胜浩
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
Stay behind the line.
留在队伍后面。
You can go now.
你现在可以离开了。
Hallo?
哈啰？
What's up?
这是怎么回事？
Is it urgent?
紧急吗？
I said I'll call when it's all over.
我说等事情结束了我再打电话。
Dohyung told me everything.
道亨把一切都告诉了我。
Let's meet to talk.
我们见面谈谈吧。
Hello. do you remember me?
你好。你还记得我吗？
And.
和。
The captain of our crime unit wants to ask a few questions.
我们重案组的队长 想问几个问题。
He is here in person.
他本人就在这里。
Do you have a moment?
你有空吗？
Oh, sure.
哦没问题。
This direction, please.
请这个方向。
It does not take long. Get on.
不需要很长时间。 进行。
There he is.
他在那。
These are the communication protocols of the people on your list.
这些是您列表中人员的通信协议。
Jungbae and Kyungjin haven’t called the number yet.
Jungbae 和 Kyungjin 还没有拨打电话。
Here is the address of Choi Jungbae's parents.
这是崔正裴父母的地址。
These bastards need to be in touch,
这些混蛋 需要保持联系
to sell it.
卖掉它。
Dohyoung, check the logs regularly.
Dohyoung， 定期检查日志。
Aside from that,
除此之外，
You could have told me that on the phone.
你本可以在电话里告诉我这一点。
You know we don't have time.
你知道我们没有时间。
I have to go.
我得走了。
Junmo.
Junmo.
What did he say.
他说什么。
Junmo, are you ok?
君莫，你还好吗？
Am I ok?
我还好吗？
Euijeong, you know
义正你知道吗
what situation am I in or not?
我处于什么情况或不处于什么情况？
Do I look okay?
我看起来还好吗？
Say if it's too much. I help ...
说是不是太多了。 我帮 ...
Help me with what?
帮我做什么？
What can you do about this investigation?
对于这项调查你能做什么？
Stop showing up and distracting me.
别再出现了 ，别再分散我的注意力了。
Just stay out of here,
只要离开这里，
if you really want to help.
如果你真的想帮忙的话。
Junmo...
Junmo...
He said he was a police officer.
他说他是一名警察。
He had to exchange the documents.
他必须交换文件。
Damned.
该死的。
Say it very clearly. Word by word.
说得很清楚。 逐词地。
He said he was a drug detective,
他说他是一名缉毒侦探
so I did as he said.
所以我就照他说的做了。
He said he needed help with his investigation.
他说他 的调查需要帮助。
A drug investigator?
毒品调查员？
Detection?
检测？
Park Junmo.
朴俊模.
Why have you changed so much?
你为什么变化这么大？
You are a police officer. Pull yourself together.
你是一名警察。 振作起来。
I know that myself!
我自己也知道！
That's why I'm doing this investigation.
这就是我进行这项调查的原因。
Ok?
好的？
Why have I changed so much?
为什么我的变化这么大？
Who pushed me to this point?
是谁把我逼到 了这个地步？
Who dragged not only me but also Euijeong into this?
是谁 把我和义正也拖进了这件事？
Who the fuck was that?
那他妈的是谁？
-Junmo, please. -Who has me mind
- 俊模，请。 -谁有我的心思
and cost someone else their life?
并夺去了别人的生命？
It was you and fucking Cho Changsik.
是你 和他妈的曹昌植。
Hey.
嘿。
-Am I not right? -Junmo.
-我说得不对吗？ -俊模。
You know it yourself.
你自己知道。
I know how much this bothers you.
我知道这让你有多烦恼。
But you have to stay strong now.
但你现在必须保持坚强。
Junmo.
Junmo.
He's going through a lot right now.
他现在正在经历很多事情。
Please understand.
敬请谅解。
Hello, this is Seok Dohyung.
大家好，我是石道亨。
Hello, detective. Here is the hall of the police pensioners.
你好，侦探。这里是 警察养老金领取者的大厅。
Hello. What is it about?
你好。这是关于什么的？
I should call you if the person comes back.
如果那个人回来我应该给你打电话。
He was back?
他回来了？
And.
和。
He asked me to show him the document and others again .
他让我再给他看一下文件和其他东西。
But I wasn't sure.
但我不确定。
He'll be back tomorrow morning.
他明天早上就会回来。
I'll come to you immediately.
我马上来找你。
He's coming now.
他现在就来了。
Something happened?
发生了一些事？
Gangnam Union has become active again.
江南联盟再次活跃起来。
It's where private detective Cheon Jinpyung
这里是 私家侦探千镇平的所在地
Junmo's identity was revealed,
君莫的身份被揭露，
and Gangnam Union's people were back.
江南联合的人也 回来了。
I'm going there straight away.
我马上就去那里。
Please keep an eye on Jung Gicheul.
请大家多多关注郑基哲。
Dohyung.
道亨。
Be careful.
当心。
You too.
你也是。
Excuse me, sir,
对不起，先生，
Chief Seo?
徐局长？
Shouldn't we report this to the boss?
难道我们不应该向老板汇报此事吗？
We can do that once we confirm it.
一旦我们确认了，我们就可以这样做。
But is it okay to meet police officers so personally?
但如此亲自会见警察可以吗？
What's up with them?
他们怎么了？
Are they different?
它们有什么不同吗？
No, sir.
不，先生。
If you stab them, they die like us.
如果你刺伤他们， 他们就会像我们一样死去。
Hey, Euijeong.
嘿，义正。
-Hello. -Oh, hi.
-你好。 -啊，你好。
-You'll definitely pass this time. -Thanks.
——这次你一定会通过的。 -谢谢。
-Good luck!
-祝你好运！
My goodness, he must be working really hard.
我的天啊，他一定 很努力吧。
RELATIONSHIP SON: CHOI JUNGBAE
关系 儿子：崔政培
Hallo?
哈啰？
Hey, it's me.
嗨，是我。
Chief Seo, are you on your way?
苏局长，你在路上吗？
Where are they?
他们在哪里？
We have a fucking emergency at the office.
我们 办公室有紧急情况。
Choi Jungbae, that bastard...
崔正培这个混蛋……
Let's meet to talk.
我们见面谈谈吧。
I have to catch a rat first.
我得先捉老鼠。
Come here. And alone.
过来。而且独自一人。
Was?
曾是？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Write that down.
把它写下来。
It is in 361-5, Nokbeon-dong, Eunpyeong-gu.
位于恩平区绿边洞361-5 。
Nokbeon dong? Where is that?
诺克贝恩东？哪里是？
Hall of police pensioners.
警察养老金领取者大厅。
Come now.
现在来。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Gicheul.
吉舍尔。
Do you remember how you said
你还记得你怎么说吗
when someone visits Gangnam,
当有人来到江南时，
that they had to come to one of your stores ?
他们必须来到您的商店之一 ？
Your dream has come true, right?
你的梦想已经实现了，对吧？
Couldn't you stop what you're doing now?
你就不能停下 你现在正在做的事吗？
It's too dangerous.
太危险了。
Euijeong, my dream hasn't quite come true yet.
义正，我的梦想 还没有完全实现。
I said I would be the "Emperor of the Night",
我说过 我要成为“夜之皇帝”
and that I would marry you.
我会嫁给你。
Man, that was really cheesy.
伙计，那真的很俗气。
You're right. I could stop now.
你说得对。 我现在可以停下来了。
But I'm so close to the goal now,
但现在我已经很接近目标了
it would be a shame to give up.
放弃将是一种耻辱。
Do not worry.
不用担心。
I'll take care of everything.
我会处理好一切。
One second.
一秒。
-Hello? -They caught Choi Jungbae.
-你好？ -他们抓住了崔正裴。
-What? Where? -Our boys will take him to the office.
-什么？在哪里？ -我们的男孩会带他去办公室。
Okay, I'll be there soon.
好的，我很快就到。
Sorry, Euijeong, I have to go.
对不起，义正，我得走了。
What's up?
这是怎么回事？
I'll explain later. Sorry.
我稍后会解释。对不起。
Crap.
废话。
Detective Park Junmo.
侦探朴俊模。
Yu Euijeong's husband, right?
柳义正的丈夫吧？
Why are you following us like a rat?
你为什么 像老鼠一样跟着我们？
Seo Jongryeol?
徐钟烈？
So you know me.
所以你认识我。
Hey.
嘿。
"Hightech-Industriebezirk."
“高科技工业”。
"New airport in Yeongjongdo."
“永宗岛新机场。”
"International Business and Residential District."
“国际商住 区”。
"Sports facilities."
“体育设施。”
"Entertainment and tourism complex."
“娱乐 旅游综合体”。
"Maritimer Tourismuskomplex."
“海事旅游综合体”。
Sir.
先生。
Where is Chief Seo?
徐局长在哪里？
Hey, I found the cop,
嘿，我找到了警察，
who followed us and had us in his sights.
他跟踪我们并看到我们。
-I found him. -Who is this?
-我找到他了。 -这是谁？
The boss's girlfriend's husband.
老板的女朋友的丈夫。
-Open up. -What?
-打开。 -什么？
Open the fucking door!
打开他妈的门！
What should I do?
我应该怎么办？
Until I call you,
直到我给你打电话
-hide somewhere. -What?
-躲到某个地方。 -什么？
The guy in there is a cop, so hide!
里面的人是警察， 所以躲起来！
Crap.
废话。
You motherfucker.
你这个混蛋。
Damned.
该死的。
Hey.
嘿。
Chief, was ...
首领，原来是……
What's going on here?
这里发生了什么？
Park Junmo.
朴俊模.
Boss's girlfriend's husband.
老板的女朋友的丈夫。
You know him, right?
你认识他，对吧？
You said you know Yu Euijeong.
你说你认识柳义正。
Then you also know your husband.
那么你也了解你的丈夫。
Or not?
或不？
Yes, I know him.
对我认识他。
But he's a police officer.
但他是一名警察。
I thought Yu Euijeong and her husband
我还以为 柳义正和她老公
had a plan to catch us.
有计划 来抓我们。
I thought that.
我以为。
But there was more to this shit.
但这件事还有更多的事情。
Seok Dohyung from the SMPA Drug Squad.
SMPA缉毒队的石道亨。
Why did he pretend to be Park Junmo?
他为什么 要冒充朴俊模？
Hey.
嘿。
You know something about it, right?
你知道一些事情，对吧？
Well, maybe not.
嗯，也许不是。
Then we can just ask him.
那我们就可以问问他了。
He had this with him.
他随身带着这个。
Because he's a police officer.
因为他是一名警察。
Wait, Chief.
等等，酋长。
Damned.
该死的。
If we kill a police officer in the current situation,
如果我们 在目前的情况下杀了一名警察
Everything gets even more complicated.
一切都变得更加复杂。
Let's find another way.
让我们寻找另一种方式。
I'll make it easy.
我会让事情变得简单。
They finish it.
他们完成了。
Listen, Kwon Seungho.
听着，权胜浩。
I don't want to doubt you.
我不想怀疑你。
Was ...
曾是 ...
Chief,
首席，
Do you now have...
你现在有没有...
... suspect me?
……怀疑我？
My gut feeling is one of us is in cahoots with the cops.
我的直觉是我们中的一个人 与警察勾结。
Let's see who's right.
让我们看看谁是对的。
Stab him.
刺伤他。
What the ...
什么...
Stab him, you bastard!
刺死他吧，你这混蛋！
Damned.
该死的。
Subtitles by: Ingo Krallmann
字幕：Ingo Krallmann